[{"answer": "I wanted to be a business person.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 8, "question": "How did she get to the top of the business world?", "qSentId": 7}, {"answer": "You know, well, we were married for 24 years, and you know, it was great.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "You know how would you sum up marriage to the Hulk?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Do you feel that the relationship basically floundered the moment you heard he'd been unfaithful to you?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Well, in my opinion I think the reason that he had to tell me was because the woman that he was philandering with had filed a lawsuit against him, and it was probably about to be public, and I think that if he had me on his side, that they could roll it out as extortion like a lot of these celebrities do.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Why did he tell you?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Before, you know, I hadn't been in that position, so I just figured that publicly they were staying with their man because of usually politicians is what you heard.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "If you're honest when you'd seen other famous people get caught up in a scandal like that, and the woman stayed with the man, what was your view of women that did that before it happened to you?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Have you'd gone through that thought in your head and thought, I would leave him?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "You know, just a rough guess I think there might have been three or four, but, you know, that's just my guess.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "How many other women do you think there probably were?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "Did you have days when you wish you were still with him?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "I think he does.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "Does he regret it, do you think?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "You know, because we were going through so much stuff with the divorce and then, of course, my son had that tragic accident, and there was just a lot on our plate to sort out, and I think that he had already moved on to a new girlfriend by the time I had filed for divorce.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Has he tried to win you back?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "And is it 10 times worse when it has to be conducted in the public eye because you're with a famous guy?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "It was phenomenal being married to him.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "There aren't many of him to the (INAUDIBLE), are there?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "You know, I'm sure Terry trusted Nick, but he should have maybe thought a little bit more about the conditions, the fact that the boys were jet skiing all day and they were out in the hot sun.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "Do you blame Terry for the fact that he took the car out?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "It was actually shocking.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "How did you deal with that?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "John, I believe, is now out of the hospital and he's home.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "I don't.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "Do you have any contact with his family?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "Well, that was a blow.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "How did that make you feel?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "That was like a final kick in the teeth for you.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "She talks all about how she's sorry and that this love affair they had couldn't be denied, blah, blah, blah, and I was like, are you kidding me?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "You know, living with the enemy, you know?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "I bet part of you was thinking exactly that, checkmate, right?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Yeah, he is.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "I mean he's like a young Hulk, isn't he?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "He doesn't really like the idea.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "How does Terry deal with Charlie?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Well, it's go for yours.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "When you know what you want to do, do something?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "I don't think so because --", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "Pretty embarrassing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "I just love how much my husband loves my daughter.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "Do you ever have that feeling?", "qSentId": 703}, {"answer": "You give back.", "docId": "110628pmt", "aSentId": 714, "question": "Once you're a businesswoman and you've got the cover of \"Forbes Magazine,\" then what do you do?", "qSentId": 713}]